digitstrade.com 2013-06-09

# DigitsTrade Investments Online

## Privacy Policy

You have chosen to do business with DigitsTrade, and we are obligated to honor that relationship with great care, beginning with the information you have chosen to share with us. We believe that your privacy should not be compromised. At the same time, we want to offer you the array of financial products and services you need to accomplish your financial goals, being perfectly aware that the online privacy and confidentiality of your personal information is important to you and is also at the essence of our business.

We respect each visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our website only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to information collected on this website.

### The information we collect is used to

.: improve the content of our Web page

.: create investment account

.: unotify visitors about updates to our Website

.: contact consumers for marketing purposes

.: never shared with other organizations for commercial purposes

To use this website, visitors are not required to complete our registration form.

We collect user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer or member, such as survey information and/or website registrations and account information.

The information we collect is used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual visitor and is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. User-specific information provided by the member is used for contact information for the visitor and our administration.

During registration a client must give certain contact information, but we never sell or give away this information. It is only gathered to contact the user about services on our website for which s/he has expressed interest. Accurate information in registration page helps to prevent fraud.

### How and Why we obtain personal information

DigitsTrade takes great care to protect your personal information and when we use it, we do so with respect for your privacy. We may use personal information about you to service and maintain your account; process transactions in your account; respond to inquiries from you or your representative; develop, offer, and deliver services.

The privacy policies of DigitsTrade are reviewed annually. Our printed and online notices are then updated to reflect any material changes.

### How we protect your information

DigitsTrade safeguards clients' information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the highest standards to guard non-public personal information about you.

We safeguard all information you share with us. We limit the collection and use of nonpublic personal information to the minimum required to provide you with our investment and merchant services. We restrict access to your personal account information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you.

DigitsTrade is committed to safeguarding the personal information you provide us. This privacy policy describes how we handle and protect personal information we collect about individuals who apply for or receive our services. The provisions of this notice apply to former customers as well as our current customers.

We do not share information about our clients with any third parties for their independent use in marketing their products. We do not disclose nor do we reserve the right to disclose, any nonpublic personal information about our clients or former clients to anyone, except to other nonaffiliated third parties as required by law.

All information obtained by DigitsTrade is kept strictly confidential. DigitsTrade will never sell or rent any of the personal information obtained through our business for any reason. We have taken every precaution to make sure that all the personal information that we receive is maintained and disposed of when necessary in a safe and secure manner.

DigitsTrade have implemented state-of-the-art electronic security measures to prevent unauthorized access to client information. We use encryption, firewall, router, third party verification procedures and other sophisticated security software and hardware to help prevent unauthorized eavesdropping of and access to clients' confidential and private information.

DigitsTrade professional staff monitors software and hardware and takes all security measures on a regular basis.

We maintain personal information in a password-protected electronic file outside our website or its servers, and we limit access to such information to employees who need to have such information to provide services to you. We will only use such information about you to verify your identity and eligibility to receive certain services, to provide information to you about services that we believe may be of interest to you, to record your interest in products and services that we offer, and to respond to your requests for information.

DigitsTrade also limits employee access to customer information. Our employees are required to maintain and protect the confidentiality of your personal information and must follow established procedures to do so. They are trained on a regular basis to increase their awareness to privacy and security issues.

We know that you are concerned with how your personal and financial information is treated. From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Website to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Website periodically.

### Cookies

With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information. This is used to record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit.
